long time no see.
久しぶり
Cute as always
相変わらず可愛い
hey.
ね
How have you been working as an idol since then?
どう ですか、あれからアイドルの活動の方、
Is everything going well?
順調ですか?
Chewy.
もちもち
It's chewy.
もちもちね
The day when you make your major debut or become famous is coming soon.
メジャーデビューというか、有名になる日も近いですね
Didn't you just go there with me last time?
前回ちょっと僕と行ったしじゃないですか
I just remembered it now.
ちょっと今思い出した
What did you do?
あれ、どういうことしたんだっけ?
何したっけ?
picture?
え?
What did you do?
どういうことしたんだっけ?
I think I did something that made me go huff.
フフってなっちゃうようなことしたと思うんですけど
Today as well, I'll contact you to say let's meet again.
今日もね、一応あの、もう一回会おうよということで連絡させても
I came here.
ら ったんですけど
It wasn't me today, I think I had a little sex ride last time.
今日ちょっと僕じゃなくて、前回ちょっとハメ乗りしたと思うん
But.
です けど
How do I have my first sex ride?
どうやったら初めてのハメ乗り?
that's right.
そうです
Today, she called another guy instead of me.
今日ちょっと僕じゃなくて、別の男の人呼んじゃったんですよ
I called an acquaintance of mine.
僕の知り合い呼んだんですけど
As for why, I showed him the picture from last time.
なんでかって言うと、図前回の写真を見せちゃったんですよ
Well then, it's really cute.
じゃあ、めちゃめちゃ可愛いと
I want to meet you too.
俺も会いたいと
So, there are lots of them.
ということで、なくなく
There's no shortage of them.
なくなく
I liked Rand though.
ランドは僕よかったんですけどね
So, today I will be working with that person.
なので、今日はその人と形になるんですけど
Is it average even if it's not me?
僕じゃなくても平均ですか?
picture?
え?
That's sad.
悲しいね
It's sad that it looks like a flyer though.
フライターみたいなのが悲しいですけど
Well, not much, because that's what I do when I talk.
まあ、あまりね、僕がしゃべってもあれなので、
I'd like to ask you to come in right away.
早速ちょっと入ってきてもらおうと思うんですけど
How are you preparing for that?
その準備どうですか?
Well then, would you like me to come in?
じゃあ、入ってきてもらおうか
cute.
可愛い
It's really good, isn't it?
全然、実物いいですね
Are you holding a handshake event?
握手会とかやってるんですか?
Are you doing that?
やってくれてるんですか?
Handshake session.
握手会
They're shaking hands like this, not like this.
こういうとこじゃなくて、こういう握手をやってるんですよね
I got so excited that I reached the top.
興奮して真上までしちゃった
Handshake session.
握手会
Please come and do it at this stage.
こう いうステージでこんでやってください
grip
握
Hand meeting.
手 会
Are you okay?
大丈夫なんですか?
That kind of thing is like a weekly magazine.
そういうのってほら、週刊誌とか
It might be written about, right?
書かれるかもしれないじゃないですか
By that time.
そのときはもう
Are you okay.
大丈夫
That's amazing, idols these days.
すごいですね、最近のアイドル
My hands are clean.
手はきれい
Small.
ちっちゃい
How do you use your hands when holding the microphone?
マイク持つときの手はどうやるんですか?
It seems kind of naughty.
なんかやらしい
That's how I grabbed it.
そうやって握ったんだ
I grabbed it.
握ったんだ
It's normal to talk like this.
普通のね、こういう話し方
Let's talk some more.
もうちょっと話しましょうよ
Let's talk as we see it.
見えたままで話しましょうよ
Like this.
こうやって
Just as you see it.
見 えたままで
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
It's definitely pink.
さすがにピンク色
This made me wonder what I would do if I wore black.
これで黒とか履いてたらどうしようとなっちゃった
Do you wear underwear when you stand on stage?
ステージ立つときは下着履いてるの?
I'm wearing them
履いてるんだ
Yo.
よ
T-back or something.
T バックとか
When?
のとき?
There are both.
どっちもあります
Today is?
今日は?
Oh, I said something.
あ、ちょっと言っちゃった
Isn't this a queen character?
これ女王様キャラじゃないの?
Not.
じゃない
Don't you usually do this?
普段こういうことしない?
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
happy?
嬉しい?
I'm happy too.
僕も嬉しいですよ
Is a hug okay?
ハグくらい大丈夫なの?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
The hands that bought a lot of bread, the hugs, etc.
いっぱいブッパン買った手とか、ハグとか
Can I hug you, then?
ハグいいですか、じゃあ?
Feeling cold?
冷たい感じ?
Isn't it okay to just chew this as is?
これ、このままチューとかいっちゃってもいいやつでしょ?
May I?
いいですか?
Shall we try it?
チューしてみようか
Yeah, what?
ええ、何?
After all, you have to turn it properly.
やっぱちゃんと手回すんだからね
Idols are amazing.
アイドルってすごい
Are you grabbing fans when you're making noise?
騒げところでファン掴んでるの?
Hey.
ね え
I also like hands.
手も好きなんだけど
Idol's idol.
アイドルのアイドル
Are these members actually doing this too?
このメンバーとかも実はやってるんですか?
Or is it just me?
それとも私だけ?
I don't know.
わかんない
わかんないのね
What should I do?
どうする?
If it was just me.
自分だけだったら
Can I see your panties from this angle?
この角度からパンティ見てていい?
It seems pretty risqué.
結構際どそうだね
Does it seem close?
際どそうですか?
Pi
ピ
- Su?
ー ス?
So what about this underwear?
そうするともう、この下着?
We have no choice but to panic.
焦 るしかないね
Ah, that's cute.
ああ、かわいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
I'm wearing it here.
ここ着てますからね
All you have to do is take it off.
あとは脱いでくだけだよ
Great style.
すっごいスタイルいい
Do you like underwear?
下着好きなの?
下着は好きなの?
I like underwear.
下着好きです
Do you have a lot?
いっぱい持ってる?
I have a lot.
いっぱい持ってる
It makes sense, doesn't it?
筋があるじゃないですか
This is how you dance on stage.
ステージでこう踊っているとあるんだね
Are you going to play songs like Lessons?
レッスンとかの曲やるんでしょ?
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
It's like this.
こういう感じ
It's like it's spinning around here.
こっち振れ巻くみたいな
Stay firm.
しっかり足引いて
Shall I wave?
手振りますか?
I'm shocked.
びっくり込んでるよ
Isn't it too much?
あげすぎじゃない?
Have you gotten fired up?
気合い入れてきちゃったんですか?
Your legs are toned.
足引き締まってるね
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
You did it, right?
したんでしょ?
Do you feel quite sensitive?
結構、敏感な感じ?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
Chikugi is amazing.
チクギがすごいよ
I'm feeling blurry.
チクギぼっきりしてる
It's a beautiful chikugi.
綺麗なチクギだね
When you join a group, don't you show your naked body to the producer?
グループに加入するときって、プロデューサーに裸で見せないの?
Isn't there something like trying to block people out because their style is bad?
スタイル悪いと塞ぎようとか、そういうのないの?
Isn't that what it is?
そういうのじゃないの?
What is a celebrity?
芸能家って
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
How are you feeling now?
今、どんな心境なんですか?
How do you feel?
どんな心境?
Only one pair of panties.
パンティ1枚だけ
What do you think?
どうだろう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look at one last picture.
最後に一枚見て
He's the guy who bought the idol's panties.
アイドルのパンティを買った男だよ
Are you a little wet?
ちょっと濡れてる?
It'll be a little slimy.
ちょっとぬるっとするよ
I thought it was Hinada.
ひなだんだと思って
Try riding it.
乗ってみて
Spotlight, this is how we do it.
スポットライト、こうやってやってるよ
Now at the center.
センターで今
By the way, what can I say here?
ちなみに、ここ何て言うところでしょうか?
What do you say?
何て言うところですか?
I'd like to hear it from an idol's mouth.
アイドルの口から言わせてみたいんだけど
with 4 characters.
4文字で
First, it starts with O.
最初、Oから始まる
Don't you know about idols?
アイドルは分かるないの?
I don't know.
分かんない
It's Oma, Oma.
オマですね、オマ
Are you a mom?
オマですか?
Try opening it a little and turning it from the bottom.
ちょっと開いてみて、下から手回してみて
behind.
後ろ
There's a back window.
後ろ窓あるから
Do you get this wet?
こんなに濡れるの?
Isn't this dangerous?
これやばくない?
That's dangerous.
やばいよね
This is a level that is written out of habit.
これ習慣心書かれるレベルだね
I'm a fan representative and I'm so excited.
ファン代表でベロベロしてます
Did you hear this?
これ聞こえた?
now.
今
I wish I had picked up the current microphone.
今のマイク拾いたかったよね
Your pussy is a mess, isn't it?
オマンコ、くちゃくちゃだよね
Can I have you sit back like this?
こうやって座り直してもらっていい?
It feels like my pussy is sticking out a little.
ちょっとオマンコ突き出す感じ
It's like this.
こんな感じ
If you tighten your pussy like that, your fingers will come off.
そんなオマンコ締めると指取れちゃう
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
You went.
行ったね
I won't go out for a while.
ちょっと外に出ない
How do you hold the mic?
マイクどういうふうに持つんだっけ?
Try holding it like that.
そういう感じで持ってみて
What should I do with this mic?
このマイクどうするの?
Will you sing?
歌ってくれる?
You know, right?
知ってるでしょ?
As expected.
さすがに
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
It feels like it's connected.
絡める感じ
It's the same.
同じです
This is also dangerous.
これもやばいよ
this.
これ
This is also a habit.
これも習慣者ですよ
Is the group selling as normal?
グループは正常派で売ってるの?
This is bad, isn't it?
これまずいよね
This is 5 people.
これ5人なんで
What are you doing now?
今やってることは何?
There's a bed.
ベッドありますね
Fa
フ ァ
N: The representative is the bed.
ン 代表としてベッドだよ
Just open it up like this.
ちょっと開いててこうやって
Does it actually feel good?
実際のとこ気持ちいいんですか?
I'd like to hear something like that from an idol's mouth.
アイドルの口からそういうの聞きたいんですけど
Toward the TV.
テレビに向かって
It's not TV though.
テレビじゃないけど
Do you feel good now?
今気持ちいいんですか?
I can't do it anymore.
僕がもうできないんですけど
Is it raw?
生ですか?
born.
生
why?
なんで?
It feels raw.
生気持ちいいですよ
It's no good raw.
生ダメだよ
why?
なんで?
Is it bad for raw food?
生ダメなの?
It's no good unless it's raw sex.
セックスの生じゃないとダメですよ
I'm finally going out.
最後僕外出すから
It's a mess, isn't it?
めちゃめちゃだよね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
picture?
え?
Do you like this?
これ好きってこと?
It feels good raw, right?
生気持ちいいでしょ?
What is it?
何かさ、
You're saying something.
何 か言っちゃってるじゃん
Try opening it once.
一 回開いてみて
from myself
自分から
It looks like it was born.
生 まれ見えだよ
Anal, anal.
アナル、アナル
Do you know what anal is?
アナルって知ってる?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Is it okay for idols to show their butts?
アイドルがお尻見せちゃっていいの?
It's got a lot of power.
だいぶ力が出てるね
How many times have I said it?
何回言っちゃってるんですか?
Are you saying a lot?
いっぱい言ってる?
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
You're pressing against my pussy.
おまんこ押し付けてきてるね
Do you want to enter?
入れたいの?
I wasn't in it just now.
今入ってなかったけど
I want to enter.
入 れたい
Do you like this too?
これも好き?
Do you like it?
好きなんですか?
Want to try it yourself?
自分で入れてみる?
Her pussy is also wide open.
おまんこもパックリ開いちゃってるよ
I'll listen to it again.
もう一回聞くよ
Where can you see it?
どこ見られてますか?
It sounds amazing.
すごいって思って聞こえる
interesting.
面白い
Take it out next time.
つぎ出してね
He's the one who was let in, right?
入れられた人でしょ?
That's definitely true.
だ ってそれ間違いなく
I'm putting it in.
入れてる
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Try opening it.
開いてみて
You're looking really cool.
すっごいちゃんかっこよくしてるね
Are you feeling it when you grab the sheets?
シーツ掴んで感じてるの?
It's scary now.
やばいよ今
That's amazing.
すごいよ
That's how your idol feels.
君のアイドルがそんな感じてて
Do you like me?
僕好き?
Huh?
あれ?
I don't mind if I cum inside you.
中に出していいんだけど
It's not good in the middle.
中ダメだよな
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
You said you'd take it outside.
外に出すって言ってたけどね
I'm out.
外出てる
外出してる
Huh?
あれ?
I'm out.
外出してるよ
Mom, forget this for once.
ママ、一回ちょっとこれ忘れて
Shall I clean it up?
きれいにしてあげようか
I'll clean it for you.
お掃除してあげる
I have to add it.
足しないと
I thought it was a microphone.
マイクだと思って
Did it come out?
出たかな?
I asked him to get on his elbows one more time.
一回もう一回肘ついてもらって
I feel like I'm trying to take it home with me.
だいぶ持って帰ろうとしてる感じするけど
Are you tightening it?
締め付けてる?
It might have been almost inside.
ほぼ奥に入ってたかもしれない
terrible.
やばい
Huh?
あれ?
Is today a normal day?
今日平気な日だっけ?
Dangerous day?
危ない日?
Dangerous day.
危ない日
I have to say that first.
それ先に言わないと
No.
ダメだよ
Timing is difficult for men.
男はタイミング難しいから
Was it okay if the sperm flowed out and made a squishy sound?
精子が流れてピュッピュッってなってもよかった?
It was a crazy hair time.
めちゃめちゃ髪タイムだったね
I was a fan.
ファンサーしてたね
Hair time was amazing.
髪タイムすごかったよ
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかったよ
Well then, get on your elbows.
じゃあさ、肘ついて
While there, I made peace.
そこでピースしながらさ
Peace.
ピースして